Previously, on AMC's "The Walking Dead"...
《行尸走肉》前情提要
I need a search party.
派一支搜索队
See if Daryl ran home like the dumb animal that he is.
看看达里尔有没有犯傻跑回家
Daryl does turn up here,
如果达里尔真在这里出现
just know there's no statute of limitations on this.
记住这事没有诉讼时效
I'm utterly, completely, stone cold Negan.
我完完全全  彻头彻尾是尼根
How many people here can fight?
这里有多少人可以战斗
Who would train all this cannon fodder?
谁来给这些炮灰训练
- I will. - Give me a week.
-我来  -给我一周时间
I memorized everything
我记下了
Daryl and Carl took Rick about the inside of Negan's place.
达里尔和卡尔给瑞克说的尼根基地内部情况
- There's only two of us. - Are you changing your mind?
-只有我们两个人  -你要改主意吗
I'm ready to kill him.
我准备好杀他了
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8
原创翻译  双语字幕
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
最新连载海外影视剧下载 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com 仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
Are you here --
你来这里是..
I'm here because I need your help.
我来这里是找你帮忙的
Sorry for taking over your trailer.
抱歉占用了你的拖车
I grew up ?with a lot of people around.
我长大时身边有很多人
I'm used to it.
我习惯了
Big family?
大家庭吗
Uh...group home.
是教养院
This isn't like that, though.
但这跟那不一样
Not the bad parts, at least.
至少没那么糟糕
For the first time, I feel like I belong.
有史以来头一回  我有了归属感
Trying to make sure you and Sasha became a part of this
努力确保你和萨沙融入
made me a part of this.
让我也融入了
When I was first here...
我刚来时
I was never here.
心不在这里
I, um...
我
I always found it hard getting close to anyone --
我总觉得接近别人很难
neighbors, friends...
邻居  朋友
boyfriends.
男友
You should try it sometime.
你有空该谈谈恋爱
Even if it doesn't last.
就算不会持续下去
I'm gonna talk to our blacksmith about making more spears.
我要跟铁匠聊聊多做几根长矛的事
Maybe we can trade with the Kingdom for some body armor.
也许我们能和神之国交换防弹衣
Thing is, what we really need is riot gear.
问题是  我们真正需要的是防暴装备
I was...
我
looking for something to read the other day.
那天在找书看
You can have the bullets.
子弹你可以留着
I didn't know you had a gun.
我不知道你有枪
I didn't.
我之前没有
I do now.
现在有了
Sasha, don't go -- not yet.
萨沙  别走  现在别走
Rosita didn't come here to train people.
罗西塔不是来这里训练人们的
You're both going after Negan.
你们都要去杀尼根
But you can't do that without people.
但没有别人的帮助  你们做不到
A lot of people.
许多人
We've talked about this.
我们谈过了
I know what you think.
我知道你的想法
And I appreciate that.
我很感激
But I'm not gonna change my mind.
但我不会改变主意
She's not.
她也不会
Does Maggie know Rosita's here yet?
玛姬知道罗西塔来了吗
Uh, I-I-I don't think so.
我想不知道
I didn't...
我没有...
You should tell her.
你该告诉她
About all of it.
告诉她一切
No. Not yet.
现在还不行
Sh--
她
I'm still -- I'm still getting ready.
我还在准备
And the thing is, Rosita is going,
问题是  罗西塔要去
with or without me.
不管有没有我
So it should be with me.
所以应该有我
- Then I'll go, too. - Me, too.
-那我也去  -我也是
No.
不行
The Hilltop has to be ready for what happens after.
山顶寨必须为之后发生的事做好准备
Maggie needs you.
玛姬需要你们
She needs you, too.
她也需要你
Not anymore.
不再需要了
She has everyone else,
她有了你们大家
and they have her.
大家有了她
You can stay.
你可以留下
I know you can.
我知道的
But I know you won't and she won't,
但我知道你不会  她也不会
but I wish you would.
但我希望你留下
'Cause it's a long life, and then it isn't.
因为你本可以长寿  如果去了就不是了
You can take anything else you need.
你需要什么都可以拿走
But you and Rosita need to talk to Maggie.
但你和罗西塔得和玛姬谈谈
You owe her that much.
这是你欠她的
Listen...
听着
Enid...
伊妮德
Maggie trusts you.
玛姬信任你
You have to protect her, no matter what.
你得保护她  无论发生什么
She's the future of this place.
她是这里的未来
I know it.
我知道
So are you.
你也是
Hold on to this for me.
帮我保管
It's for the baby.
这是给孩子的
Maybe you can work on it while I'm gone.
也许我走后你能继续编
Okay.
好
Sasha...
萨沙
Yeah.
嗯
In 10 minutes,
十分钟后
I'm gonna tell Maggie what's going on.
我会告诉玛姬发生了什么
It's up to you what you want to do with that.
在此期间  你想怎么做是你的事
I'm doing what you asked.
我照你的吩咐做了
The Saviors are coming!
救世军来了
We have to get Maggie.
我们得去找玛姬
- Where is she? ?- Come on!
-她在哪  -快来
Where do we hide?
我们躲在哪
We're not hiding.
我们不躲
All right, get in.
好  进来
It goes to the other side.
这通往另一头
We got to get out before Maggie does.
我们得赶在玛姬之前出去
We'll never make it in time.
我们来不及的
Come on!
快
Just stay down there.
待在下面
I'll keep them away.
我来引开他们
They aren't the same ones who came to Alexandria.
这不是去亚历山大的那批人
Simon! Hello.
西蒙  你好啊
Right back at you, Gregory.
你也好啊  格雷戈里
Hello.
你好
We weren't, uh, expecting you back so soon.
我们没料到你这么快就回来了
You want to talk in my office?
想去我办公室谈吗
I got a bottle of gin my people found.
我的人找到了一瓶琴酒
You're a gin man, right?
你喜欢喝琴酒  对吧
Oh, I'm a man of...
我的
shifting specifics of tastes in transition.
口味经常变化
I'm into tequila now.
我现在喜欢龙舌兰了
A?ejo. Reposado.
陈酿  金黄色
Sipping, mixing...
啜饮  混合
Un mundo de sabor.
口味的世界
Gin seems like turpentine.
琴酒像是松节油
It happened quick with a gimlet the other night.
那晚喝了琴蕾鸡尾酒  口味就变了
I'm an unusual kind of creature.
我是个非同寻常的人
You know what?
知道吗
I respect that.
我尊重这点
Yeah. Tequila.
嗯  龙舌兰
Mental note. Locked.
心理笔记  记住了
Great.
很好
Oh, no need to talk.
没必要闲聊了
This is hopefully a quick visit.
这是一次短暂的拜访
Well, what can I do for you?
我能为你做什么
That's an excellent question.
问得好
Alas, the answer's not so excellent.
但是啊  答案可就没那么好了
You have a certain somebody that, uh...
你这里的某个人...
now needs to be Negan's certain somebody,
现在要变成尼根的人
so what you can do for me is point me in their direction.
所以你能为我做的就是指明他所在的方向
So, who is it?
你指的是谁
You get your pointy finger up, and I'll tells ya.
你准备好带路  我就告诉你
Daryl.
达里尔
Did you dig that tunnel?
那个隧道是你挖的吗
Maggie thought we needed a quick way out.
玛姬认为我们得有个出去的捷径
So I made one.
所以我就挖了一条
Well, we're out. So now what?
我们出来了  现在怎么办
You know.
你知道的
If this one starts, I'll siphon some gas.
假如这辆能点着  我会抽走一些油
I just got to find --
我只要找到...
There's an empty water bottle.
那里有个空水瓶
I thought this was the one, but...
我以为这辆能点着  但是...
Like it?
喜欢吗
I made it.
我做的
Car's dead.
这车点不着
Where'd you learn to disarm bombs?
你在哪儿学的拆弹
Were you in the Army?
你之前是军队的吗
Someone I knew.
我认识的一个人教我的
Not him.
不是他
Listen, I'm not here to play "Get to Know You,"
听着  我不是来玩"相互了解"的
so either we talk about the mission or we don't.
所以我们要么谈任务  要么不说话
Okay.
好吧
Jesus said there's some buildings,
耶稣说有几栋建筑
two, three, four stories,
二三四层楼高
just outside the sanctuary to the east of it.
就在救世堂外的东边
At least one of them should have a line of sight to the rear courtyard,
那些建筑中至少有一栋能看到他们的后院
past the fence with the walkers on it.
就在行尸围栏后面
We hole up, we wait, we take a shot from there.
我们躲起来  等着  然后从那里狙击
If we have to get closer,
如果我们不得不靠近
there's some weak spots in the perimeter
外围有一些薄弱点
we might still be able to take advantage of,
或许我们可以利用
but if we can,
但假如可以的话
I say we stay outside, do it clean.
我还是建议我们待在外面  做得干净些
Maybe make it out of there alive.
也许还能活着回来
You see a problem with that?
你有意见吗
I want to make sure we get him.
我想确保我们杀了他
That means we go in.
那就意味着我们得进去
If we shoot from a distance and miss,
假如我们在远处射偏了
we don't get another chance.
就没有第二次机会了
I won't miss.
我不会射偏的
Even if you shoot and graze him, he doesn't die.
就算你射伤了他  他也死不了
If we go in and get caught --
假如我们进去被抓住了...
I won't get caught.
我不会被抓住的
What the hell's wrong with you?
你到底有什么毛病
They take us, we don't get another try.
被抓住就没第二次机会了
Because they'll kill us.
因为他们会杀了我们
If we're out here, we're alive.
如果我们待在外面  还能活命
We get another go.
还有第二次机会
Nothing is wrong with me, Sasha.
我没什么毛病  萨沙
I'm gonna make sure he's dead.
我要确保杀死他
Look, if this is too much for you,
假如这对你而言太过了
you want to bail, now's your chance.
你想要退出  现在可以走
I'm not going anywhere.
我哪里也不去
- Well, I'm done talking about it. - Good.
-我已经受够谈论这个了  -很好
Maybe you'll think about it.
也许你会考虑一下
Maybe you'll change your mind
也许你会重新想想
about what it takes to get what you want.
该以什么代价达成目标
- I've got fresh veggies. - Stop.
-我这有鲜菜  -停
They're vegetables.
它们是蔬菜
Use the whole word.
用全称
We have time.
我们有的是时间
Okay.
好吧
I have these vegetables they told me to bring over,
我有蔬菜  他们让我拿过来
and the basket's pretty heavy.
而且  篮子很重
For me, I mean.
对我来说很重
Probably not you. Uh, here.
对你可能不重  拿着
Load them in the truck,
装到卡车上去
and, uh, if you meet me by the garden,
如果你来菜园那边找我
- I can get you the rest... - ?Stop.
-我可以把剩下的...  -停
I don't know who you think I am or who we are.
我不知道你以为我或我们是什么人
Load them yourself. I'm busy.
自己装车  我很忙
- Sorry. I'm sorry. - Girl,
-抱歉  很抱歉  -姑娘
pick that shit up right now and scram.
赶紧捡起来  然后滚开
And I'll take that.
这个我收了
Now.
快点
Don't make me cut it off you, girl.
别逼我弄死你  姑娘
Dr. Harlan Carson, correct?
哈兰・卡森医生吗
Do you need a checkup?
你需要检查吗
Probably. It's been a few years,
也许吧  好几年没查过了
but I'm not here for that.
但我不是为这个来的
We already gave you as much medicine as we could spare
上次你们来的时候  我们已经把
- the last time you were here. - ?Yes, you did.
-能交的药都交出来了  -没错
But we're not here to take more of that.
但我们不是来要药的
Congratulations!
祝贺你
You're moving up in the world.
你升职了
Negan wants you where he is.
尼根要你住过去
You're an important fellow, Harlan.
你是个重要人物  哈兰
You're coming with us.
跟我们走
Look, I -- I have patients here that need me.
听着  这里有病人需要我
Why does Negan need two doctors?
尼根为什么要两个医生
Well, I think my look may have conveyed the information.
我想我的表情已经传达了信息
People say I have an expressive face.
大家都说我的脸很传神
But if not, let me repeat your question.
但如果不够传神  我来重复你的问题
Why do we need two doctors?
我们为什么要两个医生
Answer - we don't.
回答是  不需要两个
So...
所以
my brother pissed someone off, get himself killed?
我哥哥惹恼了什么人  所以被杀了吗
Something like that.
差不多吧
Very, very ugly stuff.
非常残忍可怖
My condolences.
节哀顺变
But it's time.
但是  该走了
All of my charts are in order.
我的病历都是整理好的
You need to make arrangements for some kind of medical care here,
你得对这里的医疗方案做一些安排
especially for my ongoing patients.
特别是我的长期病患
I will.
我会的
- I need to pack. - You don't.
-我得收拾行李  -不用了
We have everything you need,
你要的东西我们都有
and what we don't, we'll get.
没有的我们也会弄来
Hey, you like ice cream?
你喜欢冰淇淋吗
We have ice cream.
我们有冰淇淋
We have a lady ?that makes cardamom gelato.
我们有位女士会做小豆蔻冰淇淋
Shit you not.
不骗你
Oh! Almost forgot. Set that down.
差点忘了  把那个放下
Well, fair is fair.
要公平合理
We're not leaving you high and dry
涉及到医疗方案
when it comes to medical solutions.
我们可不会让你们孤立无援
Go on.
去看看吧
Simon, a word?
西蒙  能和你谈谈吗
Look,
听着
I think I've proven that I can work with Negan.
我觉得我已经证明了我能和尼根合作
I'm a can-do guy,
我能做到
but I got to hang on to my peoples' trust.
但我需要我的人信任我
Otherwise, you don't know who might take over.
不然  你不知道谁会取代我
You know, someone else might not be so cooperative.
其他人可能不怎么想合作
They might have crazy ideas.
他们可能有很疯狂的想法
Who might take over?
谁会取代你
- What crazy ideas? - I don't know.
-什么疯狂的想法  -我不知道
I'm just considering worst-case scenarios.
我只是在考虑最坏的情况
You know, What I'm saying is,
我想说的是
I know human nature, and it isn't inconceivable.
我了解人性  不难揣测
I hear your concern.
我明白你的担忧
I'm not insensitive to it. Mm. ?Right?
我也不是不知道  对吧
If you're having problems of that nature...
如果你担心那种问题...
come to see me.
就来找我
Anytime.
随时都可以
I don't know where to go.
我不知道去哪里找你
I'll arrange it so that...
我会安排的...
...you just tell the guard who you are...
你只要告诉守卫你是谁...
...and he'll let you right in.
他就会放你进来
Long as ?there's no shenanigans afoot.
只要你别耍什么花招
There will be none.
没有花招
- I just -- I just would like you to consider -- - Wonderful.
-我只是想让你考虑一下  -很好
We'll crack open some tequila.
我们会开几瓶龙舌兰
We'll talk.
我们会聊聊
We'll work it out.
我们会解决的
You're a good producer for us.
你是一名优秀的生产者
- I don't want you to be so stressed. - Yeah.
-我不想你压力太大  -好吧
I'd be a lot less stressed if you'd leave my doctor.
如果你能放了我的医生  我压力会小很多
Gregory...
格雷戈里
Got it. Okay.
明白了  没问题
I won't ask again.
我不会再要求了
?You were gonna kill that guy.
你打算杀了那人
He was gonna find us.
他会发现我们
He wasn't, and he didn't.
他不会  他也没找到
He deserved to die.
他该死
Ever since you got here,
你来到这里以后
you haven't said a word to me.
你还没和我说过一句话
Would you look at me?
你能看着我吗
Please?
求你了
Daryl...
达里尔
I'm sorry.
对不起
It wasn't your fault.
那不是你的错
It was.
是我的错
No.
不
It wasn't.
不是的
You're one of the good things in this world.
你是这世上仅存的善与美好
That's what Glenn thought.
格伦一直是这么想的
And he would know,
他肯定不会错
'cause he was ?one of the good things, too.
因为他也是这世上仅存的善与美好
And, uh...
而且...
I wanted to kill that guy, too.
我也想杀了那人
I wanted to string them all up and watch them die.
我想把他们都绑起来  看着他们死去
But we have to win.
但我们必须要赢
Help me win.
帮我赢
This'll work.
没问题的
Now.
现在
?Get in!
上车
?Anything?
有情况吗
Negan still hasn't come out.
尼根还是没出来
But Eugene's out there.
不过尤金在外面
Eugene?
尤金
It looks like...
看起来
he's ordering people around.
他似乎在指挥别人
Playing some angle.
有他自己的打算吧
Will you teach me those knots?
能教教我怎么系这种绳结吗
I know a bunch, but not those.
我知道很多种  但没见过这种
Won't matter soon.
很快  这些都不重要了
It might.
或许重要呢
Yeah, I'll show you.
好吧  我教你
All right, here's the first one.
首先是第一个
Cross it over your hand like that.
像这样在你手里交叉
Then you take the top loop, bring it down, up,
然后把上面这一圈拉下来  折上去
and back through, then...
从后面穿过来  然后这样
Got it?
会了吗
Let me try.
我试试
You know...
你知道吗
we got lucky, having you with us.
我们很幸运有你跟我们在一起
You know how to do everything.
你什么都知道
Johnny.
约翰尼
That's who taught me about bombs.
我关于炸弹的知识都是他教的
Survivalist, prepper-type shit.
他是个生存主义者  "有备族"什么的
Marcus taught me about cars.
关于车的知识是马库斯教的
He was a mechanic...
他是个技工
and a wannabe stunt driver.
一心想做个特技车手
And an asshole.
混球一个
Knot-tying was from Chaser.
绳结是猎人教的
Yeah, that wasn't his real name.
当然  他真名不叫这个
There were others.
还有其他一些人
Were those people you lost on the way to D.C.?
是你去华盛顿的路上失去的那些伙伴吗
No, not them.
不  不是他们
A lot of guys wanted to protect me,
有很多人想要保护我
like there was no way i could know how to take care of myself.
就好像我自己完全保护不了自己一样
And I didn't.
我当时确实保护不了
And I hated the way that felt.
我讨厌那种感觉
So I rolled with it.
所以我顺着他们来
They didn't even notice I was picking up
他们甚至都没有注意到
everything they knew how to do and doing it better.
我把他们的东西都学会了  还比他们做得更好
Then I'd outgrow them and bounce.
我比他们强了就离开了
The sex was just for fun.
做爱只是觉得好玩
When the world's over,
世界都玩完了
everyone should be getting their rocks off.
大家都该随心所欲些
Was that how it was with him?
你跟他也只是这样吗
Abraham?
亚伯拉罕
No.
不是
I fell in with him
我爱上他了
because he saw I could handle my shit.
因为他看到了我能保护好自己
And I never looked back.
我以前从不回头
Well, no, I did.
不  我回头了
When it was over.
在我们分手时
Yeah.
是啊
You know the thing that killed me?
你知道我最受不了的是什么吗
When we got to Alexandria,
我们到亚历山大以后
I was acting like I was all good 'cause he wasn't.
我表现得像完全没事一样  而他不是
Then, the son of a bitch was actually all good.
然后  那个混蛋倒是真的完全没事了
And I couldn't figure this one out.
我就是想不明白
Living there, feeling like we had made it,
在那里生活着  好像我们已经成功了
I couldn't pick that up.
我就是适应不了
Then, when he bounced, I...
然后  当他离开  我...
...I thought I hated you.
我以为我恨你
But maybe I just hated
但也许我恨的只是
that he figured out his shit first.
他先搞明白了自己的破事
I've never told anyone any of that stuff.
我从来没和任何人说过这些
Who I was, what I did...
我曾是谁  我做过什么
I'm glad...
我很高兴
that you felt like...
你觉得你可以
you could.
跟我说
I was stupid to waste so much time.
我太蠢了  浪费了那么多时间
Now I'll never get to tell Abraham
现在我再也没有机会告诉亚伯拉罕
I'm happy he was happy.
他快乐令我也感到快乐
Were you happy?
你当时快乐吗
I was.
快乐
It wasn't his time.
他命不该绝
Abraham would've wanted to go out fighting.
亚伯拉罕会想在抗争中死去
And that asshole with the bat took that away, too.
那个拿球棒的混球连这个机会都不给
To go out with a point to going out.
死的要有意义
I guess we all want that.
我猜这是我们所有人都想要的
No matter how it all goes down,
无论最后变成什么样
I got your back.
我是你的后盾
And I've got yours.
我也是你的后盾
You think that prick's out there yet?
你觉得那个混球出来了吗
Oh...shit.
该死
What?
怎么了
Dr. Carson, Maggie's doctor.
卡森医生  玛姬的医生
They brought him here.
他们把他带来了
Negan's out.
尼根出来了
Oh, he's too close.
他离得太近了
Ah, I can't get a clean shot.
我瞄不到他
Turn on the walkie.
打开对讲机
This is Dr. Eugene Porter, Chief Engineer, speaking.
我是尤金・伯特博士  首席工程师
I'm gonna need a dozen more walkers,
我还需要一打行尸
a.k.a. "dead ones" in the local parlance,
按本地说法  也就是死尸
for expanding the fence protocol PDQ.
用来扩展围栏方案  立刻去做
Actually, PFQ.
立刻他妈去做
This is per Negan, who I also am,
这是尼根的要求  我也是尼根
even if it takes all night to procure them,
即便抓它们要一晚上时间
so I need able-bodied persons out there
所以我需要派体格健全的人出去
in the surrounding blocks of buildings
在附近街区搜寻抓获
snoopin' and snatchin', stat.
立马出发
Negan will be indisposed in the boudoir,
尼根会在后宫歇息  不宜见客
so in the meantime,
所以在此期间
any questions should be directed to yours truly.
一切问题都直接向我汇报
Dr. Eugene Porter, Chief Engineer,
尤金・伯特博士  首席工程师
also known as Negan, who I am.
又名尼根  也就是我
Change of plans.
计划改变
So we go in.
我们进去
I'm ready.
我准备好了
Come in.
进来
Freddie said you wanted to see me?
弗莱迪说你找我
Yes, have a seat.
是的  坐吧
I noticed you've been slacking on your scavenging
我发现你最近搜索补给和招募新人
and recruiting lately.
都很不用心
And there are too many people in your trailer.
而且你拖车里的人太多了
Fire hazard.
火灾隐患
Plenty of room here at Barrington House for our guests.
巴林顿公馆还有很多空房可供客人居住
Speaking of which,
说到这个
I have job assignments for the newcomers.
我给新人们安排了工作
People are gonna stay, they're gonna chip in.
他们想留下来  就得分担工作
No more free rides on the teat.
别再想搭便车了
You let them take Dr. Carson.
你任他们带走了卡森医生
Surprised you didn't kneel again.
很惊讶你这次没下跪
You must be really worried
这么急着分开大家
if you're trying to split everyone up.
看来你一定很担心
Shouldn't talk to me like that.
你不该用那种口气跟我说话
Who knows what might happen
谁知道救世军
with all these Saviors coming around?
来的时候会发生什么呢
Did you just threaten me?
你刚是在威胁我吗
I was being sarcastic, okay?
我只是在讽刺  好吗
No, I think you just threatened me.
不  我觉得你刚是在威胁我
Think what you want.
随你怎么想
You know, what I'm saying is,
我只是想说
I look out for my friends,
我会关照朋友
and I realized... we're not friends.
而我意识到  我们不是朋友
?Come in.
进
Ah, wonderful -- tequila.
非常好  龙舌兰
Crack that open for me, would you?
给我打开  好吗
You may go now.
你可以出去了
Show him out, will you, Kal?
带他出去  凯尔
Everything okay?
没出什么事吧
Where's Sasha and Rosita?
萨沙和罗西塔在哪
You see that over there?
看到那个了吗
That is a half-assed attempt at a safety protocol.
那是个半瓶子晃荡的安全措施
We need a full-assed, full-court press.
我们要周密  全面的防守
That stuff out front with the spikes and the chains and the heads,
前面的那些尖矛  铁链  头颅
that's good for the optics.
视觉效果很好
It sends a message to would-be intruders
给潜在的入侵者释放了
of the "Don't Mess with Texas" Variety.
"别惹老子"的信息
But we need to drill down on actual safety protocol,
但我们要深入探讨一下真正的安全措施
especially at points that have proven to be janky.
尤其是那些已被证明的薄弱点
Well, yeah.
好
That's why I'm on guard duty now.
所以才换我来值守
No offense to that last guy,
无意冒犯前一个人
but he could hardly handle a gun.
但他连枪都拿不稳
Get up. You're getting out.
起来  你要出去了
Eugene, get up.
尤金  起来
We're breaking you out.
我们救你出去
Eugene!
尤金
No.
不
I'm not going with you.
我不跟你们走
What?
什么
I didn't ask you to come, so go.
我没让你们来  所以走吧
People got to be en route.
肯定有人来了
That weak, lying sack of shit.
懦弱  骗人的混蛋
This is it.
就现在
I'm going in.
我进了
Hold on.
等等
This is gonna take a second.
这得花点时间
More could be coming back.
可能有更多人来
Keep an eye out.
注意周围
Just another second.
马上就好
What the hell are you doing?
你在做什么
Go.
走吧
It's not your time.
你命不该绝
There's got to be a point to it, right?
必须有所意义  对吗
They need you.
他们需要你
Damn it.
该死